[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "IULIANI (R), FORMER NYC MAYOR (via telephone): How are you, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["IULIANI", "(", "R", ")", ",", "FORMER", "NYC", "MAYOR", "(", "via", "telephone", ")", ":", "How", "are", "you", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ":", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "I'm good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Was that coincidence?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "coincidence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "It was.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Is he the best candidate for this job, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "the", "best", "candidate", "for", "this", "job", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Well, we're going to have to see.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "have", "to", "see", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "Given the data that is coming out in the last 48 hours about jobs, about house prices and so on, do you believe now that this will be determined, as it often is, about the economy?", "question_tokens": ["Given", "the", "data", "that", "is", "coming", "out", "in", "the", "last", "48", "hours", "about", "jobs", ",", "about", "house", "prices", "and", "so", "on", ",", "do", "you", "believe", "now", "that", "this", "will", "be", "determined", ",", "as", "it", "often", "is", ",", "about", "the", "economy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Is the time coming when you need to say yes or no?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "time", "coming", "when", "you", "need", "to", "say", "yes", "or", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald"]}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "What would yours be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "yours", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "I have a different view than Donald.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "a", "different", "view", "than", "Donald", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Do you stand by that now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "stand", "by", "that", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "No, I never said that.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "never", "said", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Would you ever consider running with her, Rudy?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "ever", "consider", "running", "with", "her", ",", "Rudy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "I wouldn't consider running with anybody at this point.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "consider", "running", "with", "anybody", "at", "this", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rudy?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1994"], "PERSON": ["Anthony"]}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "What is going on here, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "going", "on", "here", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Well, I know Anthony from the time that he was a city council member and I was a mayor back in 1994.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "know", "Anthony", "from", "the", "time", "that", "he", "was", "a", "city", "council", "member", "and", "I", "was", "a", "mayor", "back", "in", "1994", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "How many times did he take pictures like that that he can't remember whether he took it or not?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "did", "he", "take", "pictures", "like", "that", "that", "he", "ca", "n't", "remember", "whether", "he", "took", "it", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "That's the point.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Was he right to do that?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "right", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "First of all, I think they had every right to take them to the baseball game.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "they", "had", "every", "right", "to", "take", "them", "to", "the", "baseball", "game", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Wanda, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Wanda", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "I'm quite well, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "quite", "well", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "And you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Well, I had all these sort of carefully choreographed questions for you -- the usual kind of stuff.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "had", "all", "these", "sort", "of", "carefully", "choreographed", "questions", "for", "you", "--", "the", "usual", "kind", "of", "stuff", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Wanda Sykes"]}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "What's going on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "Well, first of all, I just want to say I am very flattered that when it comes to sex scandals, that you thought of me because usually people don't go, Wanda Sykes, let's talk sex.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "just", "want", "to", "say", "I", "am", "very", "flattered", "that", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "sex", "scandals", ",", "that", "you", "thought", "of", "me", "because", "usually", "people", "do", "n't", "go", ",", "Wanda", "Sykes", ",", "let", "'s", "talk", "sex", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "What do you think of Weiner-gate?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "Weiner-gate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "You know, first -- OK, here's the thing.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "first", "--", "OK", ",", "here", "'s", "the", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Do you believe it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "I tweet now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "tweet", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Have you found any yet?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "found", "any", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "No yet.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Are you ever shocked by the sheer volume of sex scandals of politicians in particular?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "ever", "shocked", "by", "the", "sheer", "volume", "of", "sex", "scandals", "of", "politicians", "in", "particular", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Why do they all do this kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "they", "all", "do", "this", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Because they're -- one, they're people in power.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "they", "'re", "--", "one", ",", "they", "'re", "people", "in", "power", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "We talking about his movies or as a person?", "question_tokens": ["We", "talking", "about", "his", "movies", "or", "as", "a", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "What is it about -- I mean, we've talked about men in powerful positions, but what is it about the risk taking that goes on, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "about", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "we", "'ve", "talked", "about", "men", "in", "powerful", "positions", ",", "but", "what", "is", "it", "about", "the", "risk", "taking", "that", "goes", "on", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Sometimes I think that they want to get caught, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["Sometimes", "I", "think", "that", "they", "want", "to", "get", "caught", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "ORGAN: I mean, what do you think of men?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "I", "mean", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "men", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "A lot of my good friends, they're men.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "lot", "of", "my", "good", "friends", ",", "they", "'re", "men", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Do you go along with that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "go", "along", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Do you think all men are susceptible to temptation?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "all", "men", "are", "susceptible", "to", "temptation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "I think all people are susceptible to temptation.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "all", "people", "are", "susceptible", "to", "temptation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "How's he doing, the half white guy?", "question_tokens": ["How", "'s", "he", "doing", ",", "the", "half", "white", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "I'm still rooting for the black president.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "still", "rooting", "for", "the", "black", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Let's just go blow stuff up, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "just", "go", "blow", "stuff", "up", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "I mean, having said that, we have the big Bin Laden thing recently --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "having", "said", "that", ",", "we", "have", "the", "big", "Bin", "Laden", "thing", "recently", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Do you think that America is more or less racist since it's had its first African-American president?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "America", "is", "more", "or", "less", "racist", "since", "it", "'s", "had", "its", "first", "African-American", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "YKES: I think it's -- OK, I think it's less racist because we elected an African-American president.", "answer_tokens": ["YKES", ":", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "--", "OK", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "less", "racist", "because", "we", "elected", "an", "African-American", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "No one's ever asked any white political leader, where were you born?", "question_tokens": ["No", "one", "'s", "ever", "asked", "any", "white", "political", "leader", ",", "where", "were", "you", "born", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Where were you born, right.", "answer_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "born", ",", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Trump"]}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "EX", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "So whether they intended it or not, the birther crowd, you know, I don't think Donald Trump's a racist for a moment, but I think a lot of people that latched onto that campaign was certainly bordering on racism, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "whether", "they", "intended", "it", "or", "not", ",", "the", "birther", "crowd", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "Donald", "Trump", "'s", "a", "racist", "for", "a", "moment", ",", "but", "I", "think", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "that", "latched", "onto", "that", "campaign", "was", "certainly", "bordering", "on", "racism", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "I would throw Donald Trump in there, too.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "throw", "Donald", "Trump", "in", "there", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Trump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "What is it -- what is it based on if it's not race?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "--", "what", "is", "it", "based", "on", "if", "it", "'s", "not", "race", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Come on, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Come", "on", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Is that better?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "better", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "That's better.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Do you really think it's harder to be gay than black?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "really", "think", "it", "'s", "harder", "to", "be", "gay", "than", "black", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Yes, I believe that.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "believe", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NN", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "But today -- now I'm not talking about the history of, you know, black people -- African-Americans.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "today", "--", "now", "I", "'m", "not", "talking", "about", "the", "history", "of", ",", "you", "know", ",", "black", "people", "--", "African-Americans", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Just right now in American for example -- harder to be gay in America than be black?", "question_tokens": ["Just", "right", "now", "in", "American", "for", "example", "--", "harder", "to", "be", "gay", "in", "America", "than", "be", "black", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", ":", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["millions of dollars"]}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "RB", "NN", ",", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Well, I don't know of organizations and groups, you know, like Focus on the Family and such -- you know, anti-gay organizations who are putting up so much money, millions and millions of dollars into stopping me from, you know, being black or telling me that I can't, you know, exercise my blackness or whatever.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "of", "organizations", "and", "groups", ",", "you", "know", ",", "like", "Focus", "on", "the", "Family", "and", "such", "--", "you", "know", ",", "anti-gay", "organizations", "who", "are", "putting", "up", "so", "much", "money", ",", "millions", "and", "millions", "of", "dollars", "into", "stopping", "me", "from", ",", "you", "know", ",", "being", "black", "or", "telling", "me", "that", "I", "ca", "n't", ",", "you", "know", ",", "exercise", "my", "blackness", "or", "whatever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Am I right in saying that?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "in", "saying", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "As you got up to make it, knowing what you were about to do, how did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["As", "you", "got", "up", "to", "make", "it", ",", "knowing", "what", "you", "were", "about", "to", "do", ",", "how", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Um, liberated and also it wasn't an in your face.", "answer_tokens": ["Um", ",", "liberated", "and", "also", "it", "was", "n't", "an", "in", "your", "face", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ",", "CC", "RB", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "What was the best and worst thing about coming out for you, when you look back over the period since?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "best", "and", "worst", "thing", "about", "coming", "out", "for", "you", ",", "when", "you", "look", "back", "over", "the", "period", "since", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "CC", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "Best thing is just now that there's this -- not that I was hiding before, but now there is absolutely nothing to hide.", "answer_tokens": ["Best", "thing", "is", "just", "now", "that", "there", "'s", "this", "--", "not", "that", "I", "was", "hiding", "before", ",", "but", "now", "there", "is", "absolutely", "nothing", "to", "hide", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "How are things now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "things", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Much better.", "answer_tokens": ["Much", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "What has helped that process?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "helped", "that", "process", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "I think time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Give them six hours to think about this before we have to talk again, right?", "question_tokens": ["Give", "them", "six", "hours", "to", "think", "about", "this", "before", "we", "have", "to", "talk", "again", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "There you go.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "you", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "Were you very nervous about making that call?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "very", "nervous", "about", "making", "that", "call", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Do you think either of your parents knew?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "either", "of", "your", "parents", "knew", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "They said they didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "said", "they", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "When he went through his point by point guide to how much he had achieved, what was your reaction, good and bad?", "question_tokens": ["When", "he", "went", "through", "his", "point", "by", "point", "guide", "to", "how", "much", "he", "had", "achieved", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", ",", "good", "and", "bad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Well, it was good.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Can I get a fancy book?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "get", "a", "fancy", "book", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Hesitant.", "answer_tokens": ["Hesitant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "If you're being overly critical, what would you say is -- he could have been pushed a bit harder?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "being", "overly", "critical", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "is", "--", "he", "could", "have", "been", "pushed", "a", "bit", "harder", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "I think he's doing it the right way.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "doing", "it", "the", "right", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "It must be great fun to make, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "must", "be", "great", "fun", "to", "make", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "It's like constant rolling improv, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "like", "constant", "rolling", "improv", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard Pryor"]}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Who is the single funniest comedian you've ever seen?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "the", "single", "funniest", "comedian", "you", "'ve", "ever", "seen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "Richard Pryor.", "answer_tokens": ["Richard", "Pryor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "And what made him such a genius?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "made", "him", "such", "a", "genius", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "His humanity, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["His", "humanity", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky"]}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "Where is the line, do you think, in that?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "the", "line", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "in", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "I love Ricky.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "Ricky", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "What is the reward that you like most from the work?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "reward", "that", "you", "like", "most", "from", "the", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Laughs.", "answer_tokens": ["Laughs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "A live laugh?", "question_tokens": ["A", "live", "laugh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "A live laugh.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "live", "laugh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Does she speak French?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "she", "speak", "French", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "She does, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "does", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "You didn't talk to her on the ferry?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "talk", "to", "her", "on", "the", "ferry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "And then you met her where, at a party?", "question_tokens": ["And", "then", "you", "met", "her", "where", ",", "at", "a", "party", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "I was walking along with my friend.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "walking", "along", "with", "my", "friend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Did you remember her from the ferry?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "remember", "her", "from", "the", "ferry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "No, but I was drunk.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "I", "was", "drunk", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "And now that whoever that person was has stepped in, are you happy?", "question_tokens": ["And", "now", "that", "whoever", "that", "person", "was", "has", "stepped", "in", ",", "are", "you", "happy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "VBD", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "I'm very happy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "very", "happy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "Christy, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Christy", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "I'm very well, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "very", "well", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "You don't really like being called a super model, do you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "really", "like", "being", "called", "a", "super", "model", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "Why not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "I don't know really what it means.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "really", "what", "it", "means", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "How did that happen?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "Well, it's my older sister.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "my", "older", "sister", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "And then the rest of the Burns boys come into play?", "question_tokens": ["And", "then", "the", "rest", "of", "the", "Burns", "boys", "come", "into", "play", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "Well, we did a lot of trips in the early couple of years that we were together, white water rafting and ski trips and different things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "did", "a", "lot", "of", "trips", "in", "the", "early", "couple", "of", "years", "that", "we", "were", "together", ",", "white", "water", "rafting", "and", "ski", "trips", "and", "different", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Burns"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "Now that you're a director, is he feeling a little bit threatened?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "that", "you", "'re", "a", "director", ",", "is", "he", "feeling", "a", "little", "bit", "threatened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["a half years ago"]}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "Why did you make this documentary?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "make", "this", "documentary", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "Well, I had my first child about seven and a half years ago.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "had", "my", "first", "child", "about", "seven", "and", "a", "half", "years", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "Are you the director?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "the", "director", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "Yes, director, financier, producer, writer.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "director", ",", "financier", ",", "producer", ",", "writer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 762, "question": "But where did you get this skill?", "question_tokens": ["But", "where", "did", "you", "get", "this", "skill", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 763, "answer": "Well, I can't say I have any training as a documentarian.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "say", "I", "have", "any", "training", "as", "a", "documentarian", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 780, "question": "What's the most important thing that you hope people take away from this film?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "most", "important", "thing", "that", "you", "hope", "people", "take", "away", "from", "this", "film", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 781, "answer": "Well, that there's hope, that a lot of the solutions, we know what they are.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "there", "'s", "hope", ",", "that", "a", "lot", "of", "the", "solutions", ",", "we", "know", "what", "they", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 791, "question": "You went to college at 25?", "question_tokens": ["You", "went", "to", "college", "at", "25", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 792, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 793, "question": "And you came out with an arts degree?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "came", "out", "with", "an", "arts", "degree", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 794, "answer": "Yes, a liberal arts degree, but I focused on comparative religion and eastern philosophy.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "a", "liberal", "arts", "degree", ",", "but", "I", "focused", "on", "comparative", "religion", "and", "eastern", "philosophy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110602pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 795, "question": "ORGAN: So quite a smart cookie, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "So", "quite", "a", "smart", "cookie", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 796, "answer": "Well, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]